AYSEL KARADAYI

Junior Software Developer

 $\$ 0884322670 @ aysel.mkaradayi@gmail.com $\mathcal Q$ https://github.com/aysieelf $\mathcal Q$ https://www.linkedin.com/in/aysieelf/ $\$ Sofia, Bulgaria



SUMMARY

I have a passion for learning and a keen interest in technology and science. I am organized, detail-oriented, and dedicated to continuous improvement. My experience in education has equipped me with strong problem-solving skills, effective communication and the ability to work well both independently and in teams.

PROJECTS

Game Dev Journey

12/2024 Sofia, Bulgaria https://github.com/aysieelf/Game-Dev-Journey A systematic approach to game development fundamentals through recreating 8 classic games with creative twists, focusing on tech stack, architecture, project management, creative elements.

Completed games:

• Tic-Tac-Toe: Pygame

Snake: Pygame

Sleepy Fox (Pong variation): Pygame

Match Score System

12/2024 Sofia, Bulgaria

https://github.com/Alpha63-Match-Score/Match_Score
Built a sports tournament management system with player
profiles, score tracking and support for both league and knockout
formats. Our project won first place!

Database: PostgreSQL

Backend: Python, FastAPI, SQLAlchemy

Frontend: HTML, CSS, Vue.js

· Authentication & Authorization: JWT

Forum System API

11/2024 Sofia, Bulgaria

https://github.com/A63-Forum-System-API/Forum_System_API Built a forum system featuring user authentication, profile management and topic creation with private messaging functionality.

Database: MariaDBBackend: Python, FastAPI

Frontend: HTML, CSS, Jinja2

• Authentication & Authorization: JWT

EXPERIENCE

Elementary School Teacher

Hristo Botev Primary School No 202 09/2019 - 04/2024 Pasarel, Bulgaria

- Successfully finished the "Teach For Bulgaria" program in 2021
- Worked as a sound engineer for the school
- Mentored new teachers from 2022-2024
- Participated in the Design Champion program Red Paper Plane

Sound Engineer

Bulgaria ON AIR Channel 07/2018 - 12/2018 Sofia, Bulgaria

- Collaborated with 2 major news channels
- Dubbed shows from English to Bulgarian weekly

EDUCATION

Alpha Python Track

Teleric Academy 07/2024 - 12/2024 Sofia, Bulgaria

Master's in Education

Paisii Hilendarski University 09/2019 - 06/2021 Plovdiv, Bulgaria

Bachelor's in Audio Engineering

New Bulgarian University 09/2014 - 06/2018 Sofia, Bulgaria

TECHNOLOGIES

Frontend

HTML CSS Jinja2 Vue.js

Backend

Pygame

Python FastAPI MySQL

SQLAIchemy MariaDB PostgreSQL

Game Development

LANGUAGES

Pixel Art

Bulgarian

Native

Proficient

Turkish

Conversational

Aseprite

STRENGTHS

Creativity

Adding distinctive touches to transform standard projects

Critical thinking

Research-driven approach to technical decisions

Attention to detail

A keen eye that won't rest until perfection

Problem-solving

Daily algorithmic practice and deliberate improvement